<archimate:ApplicationComponent
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Reference Data Management Centre [RDMC]"
    id="a84e4464-9437-41c4-9da7-47516212e718"
    documentation="Reference data is extracted from MDM and passed to RDMC which creates the specific reference data files required by Horizon&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;RDMC is the primary repository for reference data within the HNG-X System. This reference data is received from a number of sources:&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Type A Reference Data is delivered by the POL MDM system. The interface is described in BP/IFS/010&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Type B reference data is prepared by the Fujitsu Services reference data team within Customer Services in response to reference data changes requests from POL. The interface is described in RD/IFS/023.&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Type C reference data is legacy Horizon reference data. It continues to be used to support APOP Host reference data for HNG-X. The interface is described in RD/IFS/022&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;HNG-X specific reference data in XML format (this document) is the set of additional reference data which is required to support the HNG-X solution but is not included in the Type A, B or C interfaces. This reference data is referred to as Type X. This reference data includes:&#xD;&#xA;1.&#x9;Postal Services reference data&#xD;&#xA;2.&#x9;Transaction Scripts reference data&#xD;&#xA;3.&#x9;Menu Definition reference data&#xD;&#xA;4.&#x9;Pin Pad reference data&#xD;&#xA;5.&#x9;Miscellaneous other reference data&#xD;&#xA;Type X reference data is delivered as a set of XML records in files which are in XML document format. &#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;HNG-X specific reference data files (this document) is the set of non-XML deliverables which is required to support the HNG-X solution. This reference data is referred to as Type F. Delivery of Type F reference data requires delivery of the actual Type F file containing the non-XML deliverable, e.g. a logo bitmap, and an information file in XML format containing processing details about the Type F file.&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;HNG-X specific XSDs. These define the XSDs for object types which are delivered as Type X reference data. XSDs are used in RDMC for validation purposes only and the data is not distributed elsewhere within the HNG-X domain. Delivery of an XSD requires delivery of the actual XSD in one file and delivery of an information file in XML format containing details of the XSD file."/>
