<archimate:Facility
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Belfast"
    id="id-9b0878d136cb4cccadec9fa62c3bf803"
    documentation="20-30 Box files&#x9;Investigation documents&#x9;&quot;6 case files (all police liaison): -&#xA;1. Andrew Wilson Walker – Glengormley PO case. This consists of 3 lever arch files, 1 - File containing original exhibits including two master cassette tapes of interview with Mr Walker dated 19/10/2006. 2 – second file containing original exhibits including one master cassette tape of interview with Mr Walker dated 23/01/2007. 3 - Copy file with some annotations by POL investigator.&#xA;2. Elizabeth Reid – Upperlands PO case. This consists of 4 lever arch files, 1 - File containing original exhibits, including a handwritten letter from Elizabeth Reid admitting to taking the cash, dated 22/06/2009. Files 2, 3 and 4 each a copy file.&#xA;3. Janine Susan Copeland – Banbridge PO case. This consists of 4 lever arch files, 1 - Committal file containing original statements, copy of exhibits and police report to PPSNI. Files 2, 3 and 4 each containing the case original exhibits.&#xA;4. Patrick Joseph Kieran McNulty – Belfast City Crown PO case. This consists of 3 lever arch files, 1 - Copy full file inc prosecution result. 2 - Copy full file. 3 - File containing original exhibits, inc interview transcript.&#xA;5. Robert Houston Dillon - Newtownstewart PO case. This consists of 3 lever arch files, 1 - Committal file containing statements, original exhibits and master interview cassette tape. Files 2 and 3 copy committal files.&#xA;6. Margaret Ruth Johnston – Barrack Street PO case. This consists of 2 lever arch files, 1 - Committal file containing offender report, original statements and exhibits inc master interview cassette tape. 2 – Copy file.&#xA;Other files found: -&#xA;•Lisa COLEMAN – Police liaison, customer theft amounting to £10,000 where customer requesting withdrawals from a Cash Plus MasterCard which is a top up card account with no cash withdrawals permitted. The card is swiped by the PO clerk and the top up amount entered into the Horizon computer system. The amount then appears on the clerks’ screen in the customer basket as a “receipt” and the corresponding cash amount needs to be taken from the customer. In January 2014 a customer, Lisa COLEMAN, had received several withdrawal transactions over a number of weeks using a Cash Plus MasterCard. The SPMR realised she should not have paid cash on this particular type of account and that when she had keyed the requested amount into the computer system the card account was also credited by the amount. The SPMR had previously paid out the requested cash amount to the customer which subsequently doubled the loss. The Police arrested Lisa COLEMAN for theft. Lisa Coleman plead guilty to theft and was subsequently sentenced to 9 months imprisonment, suspended for 2 years&#xA;Linda NUGENT – this was my Police liaison case where Ms Nugent was found guilty of stealing cash from the PO account of an elderly customer – CCTV evidence went some way to prove the case. Linda Nugent plead guilty to stealing £37,600 and was sentenced to 18 months imprisonment suspended for two years. My green file was sent to Chesterfield after the case was closed, circa November 2020&#xA;Pat FAGAN – Police liaison, Pat FAGAN was working as a clerk at Drumantee PO and plead guilty to False Accounting and Fraud by False Representation and was sentenced to 9 months imprisonment suspended for 2 years. SPMR was to pursue civil recovery from Pat FAGAN.&#xA;Maria HOLLAND – Police liaison, Downpatrick PO clerk Maria Holland was prosecuted for theft after pleading guilty and was sentenced on 19th January 2018 to 140 hours community service. Case file submitted electronically&#xA;I also found some files relating to POL GB investigations that Suzanne Winters (my predecessor) was involved with:&#xA;Sarah Burgess-Boyd - Sarbeck Avenue Post Office, POLtd/0910/0136&#xA;Thomas George Brown – North Kenton Post office, POLtd/0809/0169&#xA;Alan Martin – Dunure Post Office, POLtd/0809/0185&#xA;John Malcolm Brown – Aughinleck Post Office, POLtd/0910/0194&#xA;Michael James Sloan – Bendooragh Post Office, POLtd/0405/0717&#xA;&#xA;&quot;"/>
