<archimate:Facility
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Atria, Spa Road, Bolton"
    id="id-53cdf544b9b84c6a859b15a8a3c3abba"
    documentation="95 files:  Current paperwork stored until archived at Chesterfield (see index tab)&#x9;Postmaster onboarding materials and initial recruitment details for postmasters/other HR materials.&#x9;&quot;See tab - Bolton - index of documents - Supplied by Jayne Pardoe&#xA;&#xA;&quot;&#xA;Bolton detail supplied by Jayne Pardoe, Head of Postmaster Onboarding - 04/04/2022&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#x9;&#xA;&#x9;Lead&#x9;Location&#x9;Description of materials &#x9;Notes/Comments&#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Postmaster assistant vetting application (P250) – this document is completed by the assistant and has all their personal data.&#x9;Paper copy received - the P250 is scanned and stored electronically, manually input onto the Experian platform. This is then indexed boxed and sent to Chesterfield for archiving weekly.&#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Postmaster assistant leaver form (301) – assistants name, DOB and date of leaving.&#x9;Paper copy received - 301 is scanned and stored electronically, boxed with the above P250 and sent to Chesterfield for archiving weekly.&#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Postmaster assistant unsuccessful &amp; appeal information&#x9;Paper copy received – scanned and stored electronically, boxed and sent to Chesterfield for archiving yearly.&#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Postmaster onboarding returned agreement documents, including agreements, guarantor forms, ATM T&amp;C’s, Outreach Addendums, Bank statements and Banking form.&#x9;Agreements that are signed and returned by onboarding postmasters, but have not yet been signed by POL . They are stored in Bolton and also scanned and uploaded to central database,  ready to be countersigned by PM Onboarding management. &#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Postmaster Onboarding countersigned agreements. &#x9;Agreements that have been signed by POL and onboarding postmaster ready to archive in Chesterfield. Before sending to Chesterfield they are scanned and uploaded centrally. &#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Notice to Leave packs&#x9;Notice to leave pack submitted by existing postmasters, they are archived in Bolton and eventually sent to Chesterfield to archive. On receipt of the NTL pack they are scanned and uploaded to the central database. &#xA;&#x9;Jayne Pardoe&#x9;Atria, Bolton&#x9;Transfer Packs&#x9;The Onsite Trainers send a transfer packs to Bolton, however this activity should be moved out of PM Onboarding as it’s now sat with Franchise Partnering. The transfer packs are stored in Bolton and eventually sent to Chesterfield. "/>
